Kunal Bodke

User Experience Designer (4+ years' experience)

www.kunalbodke.com kunalbodke1@gmail.com 317.760.1611

GPA: 3.96/4.00

GPA: 3.5/4.00

UX designer with 4+ years of hands on experience conducting user research, usability testing, and interface design with small and large teams on devices like mobile/tablet and web applications. I keep customer experiences and business goals at the center of design process while making user-centered products.

WORK EXPERIENCE

User Experience Designer, Regenstrief Institute. Inc, June 2016 to Present

- Develop storyboards, wireframes, and functional prototypes to facilitate design vision with business stakeholders
- Apply novel user research techniques to elicit user requirements from a challenging group of target audience
- Conducted formative research using card sorting technique to design an information architecture for a mobile app targeted towards health and wellness
- Created and tested a functional prototype as a part of feasibility study which won a 4 million dollars' award from NIA

UX Designer (Intern), NOMI Beauty, New York, NY Feb 2016 to May 2016

- Independently led the mobile design while collaborating with stakeholders to stay current business goals and requirements
- Simplified complex interaction patterns which increased the user engagement to the mobile app by 23%
- Conducted heuristic evaluation on internal web app to identify usability issues and improve user's workflow
- Delivered prototypes in an Agile environment for a mobile app with incremental updates scheduled every 2 weeks

UX Designer, /Halvsies, Indianapolis, IN August 2015 to May 2016

- Rapidly prototyped several interaction patterns which was well received by the Product Manager and the CEO
- Created and documented clear design guidelines and rationale which saved developer's time and effort

UX Research Assistant, IUPUI, Indianapolis, IN August 2014 to May 2016

- Conducted 30 hours of ethnographic research with Eskenazi hospital patient population and clinic staff understand patients' workflow and identify workflow barriers
- · Conducted heuristic evaluation on multiple websites to identify usability issues and improve user engagement
- Participated in design sprints to conceptualize and strategize product decisions based on user observations
- Created a functional prototype on an Android device and tested the usability with 24 older adults

Project Coordinator, Colorss Foundation, India September 2012 to August 2014

- · Organized workshops and conducted usability sessions to interview target users and elicit user's mental models
- Led the design of self-defense mobile app using user-centered design principles based which has 10,000+ installs

SKILL SET

Design: Prototyping, Wireframes, Storyboards, Interface Design, Information Architecture, Interactive Prototypes, Journey Maps **Research:** Heuristic Evaluation, Formative and Summative Usability Testing, A/B testing, Card Sorting, Task Analysis, Interviews **Tools:** Axure RP, Balsamiq, Sketch, InVision, Framer, JIRA, Adobe (Illustrator, XD)

EDUCATION